FROM ME TO YOU 2ND SEASON
THE PERSON THAT I LIKE
The midterms for the
first term have now ended.
Yes! My grades went up!
Mine did too!
All 'cause of Sadako's lecture!
Thanks so much, seriously!
It's almost time... for the school festival.
- What's all this?
- Constipation? Diuretics?
That's so scary!
Apparently, a 2nd year named
Sadako Kuronuma is growing them.
- Sadako?
- Oh I know her! I've seen her!
- Oh c'mon Joe... what are you doing dude?
- No way! Like what? Tell me! For example...
Uh, the theme for this year's
school festival will be... fantasy!
With that in mind, I want to hear
your suggestions for our class program.
- I really hope that I can participate too.
- I don't care what it is.
Just hurry up and decide.
Here! I got one! How about we
do a "Sadako's Black Magic Café"?
Wait, black magic?
She's even famous among the
first years, everyone'll come.
Maybe we could brew some tea
with her weird weeds and serve that!
What about setting up a booth
where people can go meet with her?
Yeah! Like a fortune telling thing!
Sawako is climbing
right up the social ladder.
- Yup.
- Or something like the
- night parade of demons?
- That'd be awesome!
Okay! Then let's take a vote!
- What's this?
- That one's called fish mint.
- Ah... I've seen them make tea with that.
- Gotcha. And this?
It's shiso.
- Woah, you were growing that too?
- I figured it'd be good
since it has so many uses...
- OFF to ON] Nice shot Joe!
- Thanks, man!
- Kazehaya and the guys...
- Kazehaya!
Check it out! Sadako's been growing all
kinds of different herbs in the flower
bed!
Yeah.
Hey, so, you think we can use
shiso somehow at our café? Sadako?
- Yes. Like make tea with it or something?
- Oh! Yeah! Anything can be tea
if you soak it in hot water.
- Also, what's this one over here?
- Oh, that one is rosemary and...
Rosemary? Isn't that a kind of
spice? I wonder if that could be tea too...
I do want to talk to him... but I have no
idea what to say, so the words just won't
- come out.
- Oh! That could be nice!
Is it just me? Or has the
distance between us grown?
That space... Am I the one who created it?
Well, with Sawako, I know she's at least
trying her best to find a way to talk to
him. But It just feels like he isn't
putting in the same effort, y'know like
he's lost his enthusiasm.
I wonder if something happened.
You might not be the closest to
her- you just haven't gotten past that.
This is bad. Really bad. I need to
figure out a way to fix this somehow. Oh
yeah! I'll use Ryu--
So, Ryu... He is taking you with
him? It's happening Sunday, right?
The wedding.
Oh, that? We're gonna pile
into Pop's car and zoooom there!
Okay, what time are you
leaving? Around 7 o'clock, why...?
How to apply gel eyeliner: Brush to fill
in the gaps between your eyelashes." When
you get to the part above your
pupils, then make it a bit thicker.
Let's see... "Draw the corner of the
eyes with a long downward stroke."
Oops?
Oh jeez. Now what did
you get yourself into?
Y-Yano-chin!
I-I'm begging you, can you
please help me? I-it's bad isn't it.
I used to have a doll
that looked like that.
The thing about any makeup, is
you need to have a solid base.
Yano-chin...
Huh?
- Thank you for coming here...
- It's fine, I got to see something funny.
Hey, Chizu.
Instead of techniques to make your eyes
look bigger How would you feel if I... tried
something else?
Mm yeah. Yay. Those long, narrow eyes of
yours... are actually what's charming about
you.
- Really?
- Let's work with what you have and make
them look as cute as we possibly can.
In a way, this is big for you too.
Like a moment for you to step on stage.
All that's left is to highlight with a
little bit of light pink. It'll add a nice
- soft touch.
- Look good?
Like a different person.
Whatcha think?
That is not bad.
Come on, just hurry up and go!
Alright, see ya later!
Listen, Chii! No matter what,
you and I won't drift apart okay?
Really?
Of course. I promise.
Toru, Haruka, congratulations.
What's up?
Here. It was a
beautiful wedding, wasn't it?
Yeah.
The summer tournament.
It's happening soon, right?
It's gonna be right
after the school festival.
- Do your best! Win it this time!
- So, what's up?
Go on.
You need something, right?
Thank you! Come again!
Come on. Please.
- No way.
- But why not?
I said no.
Can't you just casually give Kazehaya
some words of encouragement?! Just say
something like, "Hey, bro, don't worry
about it, you understand Sawako one
hundred percent!" or
something like that! Anything!
Still no. There's no way to say that
casually and I won't say something I don't
mean. Also, I don't want to.
- Why you have to be like thaaaaat?!
No means no!
Well, I guess I could
lend him an ear at least.
Just so you know... I'm not doing this for
you. It's for Shota. I'm a little worried
is all.
And even if he tells me something... I won't
be sharing any of it with you. And thank
you for this.
Hey, wait! Ryu!
- Thank you! You're the best!
- Shota, you aren't getting food?
Ah, go without me. I figured I'd carry
out the tools for the parade float first.
Sure.
Out of everything, I'm most
excited for the black magic café!
And we'll have Sawako's
consultation booth too.
- Hm? What's wrong?
- I... I'm not psychic.
So I don't know if I can actually be of
help to anyone for something like this.
Hey, don't worry! You just have to say
whatever comes to mind and it'll work out.
Yeah, you're pretty good
at that, you'll be okay.
Then I'll give it all I've got!
Maybe we can mix the shiso and
geranium... and make a tea blend.
Sa-da-ko!
Master!
I wanted to have a chat
with you, so are you free?
Shota. Hey... here.
Kay.
Thinking about what Chizuru was
saying... Guess I can help out a little.
Uhh...
Hm?
So, do you think that you'll tell
Kuronuma the truth, or... just stay this
way?
Oh. Your soup...
Huh?! What's that about?!
Well, I was just wondering what happened.
I don't know how to act
around her. I'm completely lost.
I never really thought about it... you know?
I just did whatever based on how I felt.
I wasn't "just trying to be nice" or
anything like that. But, then, some of the
things I did seemed like they
were starting to make her anxious.
So... I figured if that was the case,
then I should just ask her about it, but...
But you won't?
- You think that she'd ever admit it?
- You won't?
- See?
- Oh, if it isn't Shota!
- Hm?
What's wrong with eating
lunch in the school cafeteria?
A lot. Ya think you
can afford to sit around?
I think your wife's been
cheatin' on ya... with that Kento Miura.
You're wrong. Whatever it is,
it's not my business anyway.
Huh?... That means...
She broke up with you?
- I'm right, aren't I?!
- You're not!
Wait, don't tell me... You haven't
even asked her out yet. Are you kidding?
Come on. Shouldn't you express your love?
Meet in a nice spot with the sun shining
down and share your feelings. Muster up
every ounce of your puny little
maggot-like courage and proclaim your love
for each other atop the jungle gym.
H- How does this bastard
always find out about everything?!
Looks like I made it.
Now, time for some food! Oh, Ryu, you're
done eating already? -The fried rice here
is way better than the curry, you know!
- I'm sure Kuronuma doesn't even realize
how I feel.
Or maybe she's anxious because she knows.
I think they're right. I really don't
understand a single thing... about Kuronuma.
Yeah so what does that matter? As far
as I can tell, that's pretty normal.
Who do you think you are, kid?
He's not wrong...
Where did you say she was?
Kuronuma!
Um... Last time I saw, near a flower
bed with some weird plants grow-... Hey!
So isn't it great, Sadako? I mean
you're totally fitting in with the class
- now.
- Y-you really think that? Seriously?
Could this be it... what I've always
dreamed of? To find my place among my
peers?
I can't believe you're just now
recognizing this. So, even if you were the
class's outcast...
that's all in the past now.
You don't even need Kazehaya's help! Now
you know you can do just fine on your own!
You're not happy?
Did you want things to stay the same
so you'd keep Kazehaya's attention?
Uh-uh.
Being able to fit in with my class...
Wanna play?!
...Was always my ultimate goal.
Good morning.
Something I only ever
dreamed of... But then...
Kuronuma!
He'd always talk to me like it was the
most normal thing... it made me forget any
other concerns.
You're gloomy and creep everyone out, so
it's easy for you to get his attention.
I guess my gloominess was
the reason I got his attention...
Yeah, that's true.
I do feel happy, but
I'm also kinda... in shock.
Because that was... what I
admired about Kazehaya, wasn't it?
It makes sense that
you'd get the wrong idea...
...with how he acted. I mean, the way he
talked to you, of course you'd get
confused.
What?! How does he know?! He
deserves the title Master Psychic!
But I don't think he means to. He's
not trying to hurt you or anything.
But either way... it's a little insensitive.
But that's not true! You're wrong!
Kazehaya is friendly, bright and cheerful
towards everyone! He treats people fairly!
Me included! He'd greet me with
that warm smile of his all the time!
When I told him my true
feelings, he believed me.
And that's why... for the first time in my
life. I felt no distance between me and
someone else.
It's true. I grew to like him
simply because of who he was.
But for some time now... I could see...
it wasn't enough for me anymore.
And I could hardly
believe I felt like that...
It's my fault. I'm the one
who took it the wrong way.
So this whole time... you knew that?
Uhh, let's just leave it at that! Now
that I'm saying it out loud it's totally
- making me feel worse.
- Poor thing.
Such a heartbreaker... Kazehaya...
Th-That's why, I don't
really know how to say this but...
You know...
Maybe for now... it'd be best if you just
tried to keep your distance from him.
- For both your sakes.
- Wait, wha...?!
It'll be good! You'll be on your own, free
to enjoy school life however you please!
Kazehaya too, he'll be
relieved that he's finished his job--
Y'see Sadako... He has someone he likes.
I was already flat out rejected, so...
I wasn't planning on telling you, but...
Don't you think it's kinda pointless to
be so wrapped up in him? Plus, you don't
want to cause trouble
for him either, right?
That's why. How do I put this... Think of
it like being reborn! You can find a new
love somewhere else! There's a
lot of fun waiting to be had so...
Huh? Hold on! Sadako?
I see... so there really was... another girl.
Come on...
You were that serious about him?! I'm
sorry! It's just, you know, there's
probably somebody that suits you better...
It'll be okay!
You know what, Sadako?!
You're really cute when you smile!
I can't stop. I can't control myself.
Until now... I was really... spoiled by him...
Don't worry! Don't worry!
Actually, you should have more
confidence in yourself. There's a ton of
guys out there!
I mean. I'm one.
And I'd say yes... if it's you.
From the beginning It was
already clear to me... but still...
Next time: "Affection and Annoyance"